edurg.com 2015-02-14

# EDU Research Group

| 

Privacy Policy

**EduRG.com, LLC**

EduRG.com, LLC (hereinafter "EDU Research Group") shares your concern about personal privacy. EDU Research Group recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others (collectively or individually, the "Users") who use the http://EduRG.com website (the "Website") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected via the Website. EDU Research Group provides this Privacy Policy to help Users make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Website. 

**1\. General**

By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the EDU Research Group Terms of Use. Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide via the Website or through other official EDU Research Group contact remains subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the EDU Research Group Terms of Use, and/or other governing EDU Research Group policies. 

You are informed that any photograph, image, graphic, video or other content posted by Users onto the Website becomes published news or informational content, or the like, and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

Your privacy and the privacy of your answers will be respected and maintained. Your decision to participate in a study, answer specific questions, be re-contacted at another time, or discontinue your participation will be respected. You are assured that the highest standards of professional conduct will be upheld in the collection and reporting of information you provide. 

**2\. Collected Information**

EDU Research Group may collect personal information and data including, but not limited to, application and Website usage data, file transfer and viewing data, email and personal contact information, and other identifiable information. EDU Research Group may use technological means for tagging and tracking data including, but not limited to, harmless cookies, clear .GIFs, and other technologies to track and correlate data. 

Specifically, but not limited to, the following information is collected:   
a. User Provided Data: Users may provide personally identifiable information (such as a name and an email address) to EDU Research Group when choosing to participate in the various services available on the Website, such as uploading videos and/or images or other content (collectively, the "Content") for public viewing interests, entering contests, accessing promotions, responding to surveys, accessing interactive forums, or other personalized services (collectively, the "Services").   
b. Cookies: Cookies, a harmless small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters, are deployed to your computer so as to uniquely identify your presence and use. EDU Research Group may use session cookies and persistent cookies for the purpose of tracking various important data. Use of these cookies can also help to speed your access to the Website as they serve as 'reminders' as to who you are to our programming. While we recommend that you allow these cookies to perform their tasks, you may adjust your computer's settings to restrict or refuse them. However, some features or sections of the Website may not function properly, or not all, if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.   
c. Clear .GIFs: EDU Research Group may choose to utilize "clear .GIFs" to track the online usage patterns of our Users in a non-personally identifiable manner. Additionally, EDU Research Group may also use clear .GIFs in HTML-based emails dispatched to Users so as to track which emails are being opened by the recipients. This act helps EDU Research Group to determine active and inactive email addresses.   
d. Log File Data: When Users log-in to their EDU Research Group account, our servers will automatically record and archive certain information that web-browsers send whenever visiting a website. These server logs may include information vital to validating the User's authorization to access the account. Information, such as a Web request, Internet Protocol (the "IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, the date and time of the request, and other important data is necessary to validate and authorize a User's entry and activity on the Website.   
e. Data collected through the EDU Research Group Academic survey or "Questionnaire" regarding the User's personal opinions and experiences with academic institutions. 

**3\. Information Uses**

a. Personally identifiable information submitted by a User is used to operate, maintain, and provide features, general and unique, of the Website for the User's use and pleasure.   
b. All personal information, data, or content that you, the User, voluntarily disclose to the Website public areas become available to other Users and can be collected and used by others. Your account Username is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or other Content, or send messages through the Website and other Users can contact you through interactive messages and commenting. Any Content that you submit (the "User Submission") may be redistributed throughout the Internet and other media channels, and/or may be viewed by the general public through other means not controlled by EDU Research Group.   
c. EDU Research Group does use your personally identifiable and certain non-personally identifiable information, such as but not limited to, anonymous User usage data, browser type, cookies, IP addresses, click stream data, and the like, to improve the quality and use designs of the Website through analysis of this data and trends.   
d. EDU Research Group uses clear .GIFs and log file data to: (i) provide custom content and preferences; (ii) remember information necessary for logging in to your Website account so as to save you time in re-entering such information; (iii) monitor the impact and effectiveness of EDU Research Group marketing efforts; (iv) monitor aggregate metrics providing detailed data on User activities while on the Website; (v) track your submissions, entries, and status.   
e. All information collected through the Questionnaire, other than personal contact information may be shared with education institutions. Contact information collected through the Questionnaire will only be shared if you expressly state that you are interested in receiving more information from EDU Research Group. 

**4\. Disclosure of Information**

a. EDU Research Group provides personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information on Users to subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on behalf of EDU Research Group. At all times, these parties are required to agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, and we deploy reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information.   
b. EDU Research Group reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable and/or non-personally identifiable information that is believed, in good faith, to be appropriate or necessary for the purpose of enforcing the EDU Research Group Terms of Service, or other governing EDU Research Group policies. Other causes of release of data may be due to, but not limited to: (i) taking precautions against liability issues; (ii) to assist government enforcement agencies; (iii) to investigate and defend EDU Research Group against third party claims or allegations; (iv) to protect the security or integrity of the Website and/or Services; and/or (v) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of EDU Research Group, Users of the Website, or others.   
c. EDU Research Group does not share your personally identifiable information with other non-affiliated third party companies for their commercial use or marketing use without your consent, except as part of a specific program, feature, or campaign for which you will have the ability to opt-out.   
d. EDU Research Group does share non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous User data and traffic data, with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns and trends analysis for certain content, advertisements, promotions, services, and/or functionality of the Website.   
e. EDU Research Group may release any information available if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with law or the powers of government enforcement agencies. Other causes for release of information could be for needs to comply with copyright laws or to respond to a court order, subpoena, and/or search warrant. 

**5\. Decline to Accept**

You may, of course, decline to submit or allow the submission of personally identifiable information through the Website, in which case EDU Research Group may not be able to provide certain Services to you, if any at all. You may, at any time, update or edit your personal profile information and email preferences by visiting your EDU Research Group account profile page. You acknowledge and agree that any User Submission uploaded by you to the Website cannot be removed by arbitrary request and said Content remains subject to the Terms of Use. 

**6\. Links and Third Party Advertisers**

EDU Research Group allows other companies, also referred to as Third Party Advertisers, Ad Servers, or Ad Networks (collectively, the "Advertisers") to serve advertisements via the Website. These Advertisers may use technology to send directly to your Web browser advertisements and links that appear on the Website. This technology may capture certain non-personally identifiable data, such as your IP address, etc. This technology may also measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you may view on the Website. 

EDU Research Group does not provide any personally identifiable information to these Advertisers without your consent, except as part of a specific program, feature, or campaign for which you will have the ability to opt-out. However, should you click on an Advertiser offering or choose to visit an Advertiser's website, EDU Research Group highly recommends that you consult the respective privacy policy of the Advertiser for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain programs and practices of the Advertiser. EDU Research Group's Privacy Policy does not apply to, nor can EDU Research Group control, the activities of other websites or Advertisers. 

**7\. Data Security**

In an effort to provide maximum protection of User's privacy, EDU Research Group routinely utilizes commercially reasonable physical, technical, and managerial safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, EDU Research Group cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to EDU Research Group or place upon the Website and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive said transmission of personal information, EDU Research Group engages commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems and the personal information you provided to our custody. This is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, altered, disclosed, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

**8\. Children's Privacy**

EDU Research Group complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and does recognize the responsibility to protect the privacy of young children at all times and to the best of everyone's ability. For that reason, EDU Research Group does not knowingly collect or maintain any information via the Website from persons under the age of thirteen (13), and no part of our Website is directed to persons under the age of thirteen (13). If an underage person provides such information and EDU Research Group has unknowingly collected said information, then EDU Research Group will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

**9\. Transfer of Rights**

Should EDU Research Group be acquired, merged, or endeavor to become closed for business, EDU Research Group reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information collected, during the due course of business, from Users of the Website. This information may be held as part of any such acquisition, merger, sale, or other change of control or business entity status. 

In the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, assignment for the benefit of creditors, insolvency, receivership, reorganization, or the application of laws or legally recognized enforcements and/or actions, EDU Research Group may not be able to control how Users' personal information is accessed, treated, transferred, and/or used. In any of these circumstances, you hold harmless and indemnify EDU Research Group owner(s), officers, directors, employees, agents, and assignees from and against any claims of responsibility, damages, costs, debts, losses, liabilities, obligations, fees and/or expenses. 

**10\. Contact Information**

You may contact EDU Research Group Customer Service at: 

EduRG.com, LLC   
Attention: Customer Service   
4800 N. Scottsdale Rd, Suite 4500   
Scottsdale, Arizona 85251 USA   
Email: support@EduRG.com   
Toll Free (USA): 1-866-553-5621   
Direct Dial (International): (1)602-273-3247 

**11\. Changes and Updates**

This Privacy Policy may be revised at will. Such changes, edits, revisions, and/or updates will be made available by posting updated Privacy Policies to the Website. All such changed and updated Privacy Policies can be identified by way of the Date of Modification. You are advised to frequently visit the EDU Research Group Privacy Policy to determine the last Date of Modification so as to afford you the opportunity to access the most current Privacy Policy. Regardless of your visitation habits to this Privacy Policy, your continued access and use of the EDU Research Group Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy, the EDU Research Group Terms of Use, and any other governing policies of EDU Research Group, as well as any future revisions of said legal documents and policies. 

**12\. Communications**

On occasion as deemed necessary by EDU Research Group (daily, weekly, monthly, etc.), EDU Research Group will send the User various communications, such as email newsletters or alerts, account updates, and special offers targeted to the interests of the User. as determined by EDU Research Group. Said communications shall originate from EDU Research Group only and shall be conducted in compliance to Section 4, entitled "Disclosure of Information", of this Privacy Policy. At any time, the User may modify or entirely opt-out of such communications by accessing the "Email Options" link as provided in the post-login Administration section of the User's personal EDU Research Group website. 

**13\. Presiding Language**

This Agreement and all EDU Research Group policies are written and executed in English, which is considered the prevailing language for purposes of interpretation or laws of contract. If this Agreement is translated into any other language, the English version shall be considered the primary binding legal document. 

**DATE OF MODIFICATION:** January 29, 2009 

|
